So let's look at why I've made the villain
arc migration into business to
business,
which means I'm now helping small
businesses at the same time.
I'll be honest with you,
ads never worked for me.
My coaching app, every year,
we spend more in Stripe fees than we do in
ads.
Up until when I started working with
Gemflow, I also never had staff.
I recorded everything myself.
I edited everything myself.
I had no marketing team,
no marketing department.
All I've ever had was a manager.
Every component of running a seven-figure
business, I've had a business partner,
but I do all the marketing
and sales elements of it myself.
Never had assistance with content.
Had to teach myself how to use Premiere
Pro, cameras, lighting, audio,
everything.
So what I'm selling to people
is how to operate a business solo, how to
come up with ideas on your own,
how to grow your PT business on your own,
because I
didn't have anyone else helping me back in
the day.
I did the odd course here and there.
I studied under Paul Mort for a bit to
learn him my marketing, but that was it.
I also charge about 3,000 US dollars for
lifetime access to my business mentorship.
When I do one-to-one calls,
I get 1,000 US dollars an hour.
And again, I think that's a rip-off,
but people pay it because
if I give them five
actionable points in their business
and they go away and do it,
they can make way
more than that,
not to mention they're writing off the
cost.
Because when people use your fitness app,
they can't write off that cost.
When people use me in a business capacity,
their business pays for it.
It just reduces their profitability.
I made the majority of all the money I've
ever made running my own things, saying
no to brand deals and endorsements,
saying no to paid ads.
That's what people are paying me for.
No bags of protein sold.
No Gymshark endorsements.
Not selling how to get whomp
and get people to pay you to
wear clothes.
I'm not selling protein for big muscles,
swipe up.
I'm selling how to grow a solo business
because I've done it, not because I see an
opportunity to sell shovels in a gold rush